(Sheldon:)-Butterscotch scone?
-Thanks.
(Leonard:)-It's good.
-What you're tasting is respect...
(Sheldon:)...and affection.
(Sheldon:)And about a pound of Crisco.
After breakfast,
I thought we could spend the day...
(Sheldon:)...watching the final season of Babylon 5
with director commentary.
(Leonard:)You hate Babylon 5.
(Sheldon:)I do. It fails as drama, science fiction
and it's hopelessly derivative.
(Sheldon:)But you like it, and you're my friend.
(Leonard:)Okay, great.
(Leonard:)-Still not taking you to Switzerland.
-Drat.
(Sheldon:)No Frodo for you.
SHELDON: Hello.
-Hello.
(Sheldon:)Let's dispense
with the friendly banter.
(Sheldon:)I believe you know why I'm here.
(Penny:)Well, I always figured
it was to study us...
(Penny:)...discover our weaknesses,
and report back to your alien overlords.